{
    "subject": "resource/Go_West_(1940_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/writer",
    "object": "resource/Irving_Brecher",
    "human_readable": "The writer of Go West (1940 film) is Irving Brecher.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8982284665107727,
            "question": "What was Irving Brecher's role in the making of Go West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.812258780002594,
            "question": "Is Irving Brecher known for writing other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7560446262359619,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for the film Go West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6972920894622803,
            "question": "Can you name another film written by Irving Brecher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6622568368911743,
            "question": "Who directed the film Go West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4983632564544678,
            "question": "What year was the film Go West released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48944947123527527,
            "question": "What genre is the film Go West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4891180992126465,
            "question": "Was Go West a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3919628858566284,
            "question": "How did the film Go West influence later films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3151347041130066,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Irving Brecher's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The writer of Go West (1940 film) is Irving Brecher.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3920_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the film Go West influence later films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3920_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Go West a successful film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3920_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Go West?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3920_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3920_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. There are multiple mentions of Irving Brecher as the writer of the screenplay for the 1940 film \"Go West\", including in files 48.txt, 62.txt, and others."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Irving Brecher wrote the screenplay for the 1940 film \"Go West.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}